<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Tech Lists on Unoffical LevelHead Wiki</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/</link><description>Recent content in The Tech Lists on Unoffical LevelHead Wiki</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Just the Robot and the Goods</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/you-and-the-goods/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/you-and-the-goods/</guid><description>GR-18 Sprint Jump While GR-18 is sprinting, jumps gain one extra tile of height. This allows GR-18 to reach a total of 5 tiles high and 15 tiles across.
Wall Sprint (AKA Wall Wailing) While running against a wall, GR-18 does not lose sprint. This techinque can be used to maintain sprint while waiting for an obstacle to pass or a door to open.
Sprint Direction Change (AKA Aerial Disco) Normally when GR-18 changes lateral direction, sprint is lost.</description></item><item><title>All Powered Up</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/all-powered-up/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/all-powered-up/</guid><description>The tech you can perform with the various powerups in LevelHead.
Rebound Rebound Super Jump With GR-18’s back against a wall, perform a Super Jump. At the peak of the Super Jump, throw the package upwards again. Immediately rebound blast twice. Grab and jump off the package as GR-18 passes up through it. Without a wall, a more precise timing of rebound blast in one direction and then the other can be used.</description></item><item><title>Enemies and Enemy Drops</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/enemies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/enemies/</guid><description>Any Enemy Kill Jump When destroying an enemy by landing on it, hold the jump button. GR-18 will ascend 4 tiles above the top of the enemy.
Boosted Kill Jump (AKA Kill Launch) When destroying an enemy by landing on it, press the jump button immediately after destroying the enemy.GR-18 will ascend 5 tiles above the top of the enemy.
Momentum Cancel Kill Jump (AKA Fizzled Kill Jump) If you stop pressing the jump button the moment you kill the enemy.</description></item><item><title>Items</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/items/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/items/</guid><description>Any Carryable Item Boost (AKA Kick Boost) While in the air, throw any item downwards. This provides GR-18 with an extra tile of height. Any carryable, including those that don’t go down can be used to perform this.
Tech demo video :Levelhead Item Hopping Example- TripleB36 (Opening section)
Item Hop Item hopping allows GR-18 to traverse a row of Spiketrons using throwable items. While holding down and a lateral direction, repeatedly press grab.</description></item><item><title>R.I.P (Stuff that got Patched or turned into features)</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/rip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/rip/</guid><description>^Patch 0.9.8^ You no longer decelerate if you are pressing a direction key that is the same direction as your inherited Xspeed from a treadmill or a platform. You will only decelerate the inherited speed if you push *against* it.
Toe Slide Assisted Waylay Fade-away Jumping straight up off of a toe slider followed by an ariel charge into a wall causes the rebound momentum to stay, bouncing further back than possible.</description></item><item><title>The Environment</title><link>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/environment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://levelhead.wiki/tech-list/environment/</guid><description>Tech for things that GR-18 can’t take along for the adventure.
Blaster Blasted Zipper Shift See entry under Zipper
BUDD-E Respawn Invuln Respawn at a BUDD-E. GR-18 receives a few frames of invulnerability. GR-18 can bypass non-solid hazards during these frames.
Bumper Bump Jump (AKA Bumper Jump) From a solid surface, walk onto a bumper flush with the surface and press jump on contact with the bumper. GR-18 will be propelled 12 tiles upwards.</description></item></channel></rss>